怎么體現我們是一伙的
that just defeats the purpose.
戴著這鬼東西  我什么都看不到
Well I can't see in this fucking thing!
氣都喘不過來
I can't breathe in this fucking thing,
我騎馬時沒法戴
and I can't ride in this fucking thing!
滾你們的  老子不干了
Well fuck all y'all, I'm going home!
我看著我老婆干了一天  做了30個頭套
Ya know I watched my wife work all day
你們這群忘恩負義的混蛋還不領情
gettin' thirty bags to get ready for you ungrateful sonsabitches,
我聽到的全是  抱怨抱怨抱怨
and all I hear is criticize, criticize, criticize.
從現在起  別找我或我家人做事
From now on, don't ask me or mine for nothin'!
都聽好了
Now look...
別忘了我們為什么過來
Let's not forget why we're here.
我們要殺掉山那邊的黑鬼
We gotta kill a nigger over that hill there.
要給他們點教訓嘗嘗
And we gotta make a lesson outta 'em.
好吧  我不懂了
Okay, I'm confused.